TRISA TAY, CHARTERED ACCOUNTANT (CA) 46B Toh Tuck Road #05-06 Singapore 596748 (65) 9889 0012 trisa_tay@yahoo.com

A Chartered Accountant trained in Big 4 Accountancy firm, with over 20 years of experience as Financial Controller. Expert in financial & regulatory reporting, fiscal management and accounting system development.

Proven record in compliance and risk management, developing and implementing operational and financial controls that meets regulatory requirements and improved the bottomline. High level of IT literacy including Advanced Excel skills; and the ability to adapt to many different environments.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

2007 to Present (Private Equity)

ZANA CAPITAL PTE LTD

Aug 2009 to Present

(investment and support team of CMIA novated to current company)

Financial Controller

CMIA CAPITAL PARTNERS PTE LTD Jan 2007 to Jul 2009 Financial Controller

KEY RESPONSIBILITIES Leadership

- Act as a positive representative for company Finance with business stakeholders.
- Investor relations liaison.
- Report to CEO and COO.

Compliance & Risk Management

- Chief Compliance Officer overseeing entire compliance function including AML, Sanctions, Frameworks and Regulatory matters.
- Liaise with the governing and licensing authorities: Monetary Authorities of Singapore ("MAS"), the Economic Development Board of Singapore ("EDB), and SPRING Singapore.
- Regulatory Reporting to MAS, EDB, SPRING Singapore, IRAS and ACRA.
- Supervise investment guidelines monitoring / restriction.
- Capital management for regulatory purposes.
- Ensure company is kept abreast of relevant regulatory and best practices development.
- Provide compliance advice on business initiatives.
- Review marketing materials for investment products.
- Provide compliance training to improve confidence and competence of employees, and manage ad-hoc compliance related tasks.
- Authority in AML/KYC, FATCA, CRS and Dodd-Frank.
- AML/KYC checks and reporting, Dodd-Frank, FATCA & CRS reporting.
- Liaison with Rating Agency (Mercer) to ensure the Singapore structured funds meet Singapore regulatory criteria.
- Presentation of risk findings and report to the Board of Directors.
- Business Continuity Plan documentation, and testing.

Operations / Middle office

- Deal Support, including legal documentation, corporate secretarial documentation, financial modelling and deal structuring.
- Cash Management : prepare and review cash projections.
- Capital calls, distributions, co-investments and carry interest computation and accrual.
- Manage fund expenses and prepare annual budget.
- Manage requests from investors, Investment Team, internal and external stakeholders.
- Liaise with fund administrators, fund valuation service provider, brokers, corporate secretaries, legal advisors and bankers.
- Fund valuation.
- Trade settlements with brokers and prompt filing with the relevant Stock Exchanges (Singapore, Hong Kong, Germany).
- SPV management

Business Partnering

- Financial Controller with full responsibility for the accounting, compliance and operations of the funds and fund management Company (AUM S\$250 million).
- Contributed to the successful award of Capital Markets Services Licence and Tax Incentive Schemes for the funds and fund manager.
- Compliance & Risk Management
- Reviews of governance, risk, financial performance for investments.
- Directed financial planning and analysis, key reporting processes, forecasting/budgeting, tax, treasury, MIS and administrative functions through a 3-person finance & administration team.
- Review and challenge investment valuation, NAV calculations, and carry calculations.
- Perform daily cash flow.
- Review documents and provide support on investments and divestments of the Funds.
- Singapore subject matter expert Monetary Authority of Singapore ("MAS") regulations and reporting, IRAS, Goods and Services Tax, ACRA submission etc.
- Impact merger and acquisition decisions Financial due diligence and Financial modeling.
- Shared service centre provide reporting and analysis services to Investments team. Tailor reports to business unit requirements.
- Effective interaction with shareholders whilst appreciating their non-financial background.

Financial Control.

- Start-up Zana Capital Pte Ltd with successful exempt licence application. Subsequently successfully obtained Capital Markets Services ("CMS") Licence
- Remote control of Shanghai subsidiary.
- Successful fund launches in Cayman Islands and Singapore.
- Management & statutory reporting in IFRS and US GAAP for Funds, SPVs and Fund Manager.

- Consolidation of management accounts of Singapore and Shanghai subsidiary.
- Tax planning for Singapore, Shanghai offices, and Funds.
- Budgeting management and forecast
- Cash management.
- Best practices Process improvement measures.
- Quarterly Fund Report to investors.
- Presentation for financial decision-making to the Board of Directors and Advisory Committee
- Human Resource, payroll and administrative matters.
- Corporate secretarial matters.
- Led tax savings efforts for funds and co-investors.
 - Saved over U\$14 million in potential taxes through accounting and tax treatment in support of divestment SPVs.
- Liaison with auditors, bankers, legal counsel, tax consultants and investors.

Aug to Dec 2006 RESOURCES GLOBAL PROFESSIONAL (SINGAPORE) PTE LTD

Finance Associate (contract)

- Assessed and developed key controls for inventory, accounts payable, accounts receivable and payroll systems of a US subsidiary, MPV Asia (based in Malaysia), associate with Sarbanes-Oxley Section 404 certification of internal control environment.
- Internal audit testing for US subsidiary, International Flavours & Fragrances Inc. Recommended improvements of controls for intercompany, tax, accounts payable and payroll processes.

Oct 2005 to Jul 2006 OPENWAY ASIA PTE LTD

Financial Control (contract)

- Report to CEO, who is ex-CEO of VCHEQ.com.
- Budgeting, Forecast, management and statutory reporting.
- Contributed to savings of S\$100,000 by effective tax appeal.
- Tax planning for Thailand, Vietnam and Indonesia.

2003 to Sep 2005 LIBERTY MUTUAL INSURANCE EUROPE LIMITED

Financial Controller

Business Partnering

- Contributed to the successful award of Tax Incentive Schemes for the company.
- Review business cases and ensure investment decisions are made with clear understanding of their impact on net profits.
- Work closely with and influence senior management to help drive business performance.
- Challenge revenue budget of the line managers via application of finance disciplines to decision making, such as Financial modeling.
- Funding and resource allocation drive financial efficiency with

- divisions with rigorous pressure on costs and a commitment to value-for-money approach.
- Assessing risks to the delivery of business plans formulate and drive actions to mitigate them.
- Shared service centre provide reporting and analysis services to Investments team. Tailor reports to business unit requirements.
- Manage corporate project budgets and performance.
- Sharing best practices with Group CFOs on a quarterly basis.
- Perform internal audit to counter-part office in Sydney and recommended improvements in controls for business units and Finance department.

Day-to-day

- Start-up Finance & Administration Department.
- Report to the Asia-Pacific CEO based in Sydney, with dottedline reporting to the CFO based in Boston.
- Management and statutory reporting in IFRS and US GAAP.
- Tax, treasury, risk management.
- Human resources, payroll, company secretarial and administrative functions.
- Implementation of Front-end ERP system and backend system in Singapore. First mover globally to utilise GST tax reporting, cheque printing and Fixed Assets module.
- Consolidated accounting team to support Asia Pacific business.
- Savings in 4 finance headcount, approximately S\$250,000 per annum through the effective use of IT technology: 6 staff in Asia-Pacific office vs 2 staff in Singapore for the same revenue turnover.
- Sarbanes-Oxley Section 404 certification of internal control environment.
- Consolidated activities in tax
 - Saved over US\$20 million in potential taxes through financial contract review for clients to bear withholding tax.

May 2000 to Dec 2002 VCHEQ,com PTE LTD

Financial Controller

Business Partnering

- Contribute to the successful award of EDB/IDA grant of S\$3.7 million.
- Work closely with and influence senior management to help drive business performance.
- Obtained approval by the Board of Directors (consisting of international blue-chip investors) of the revenue plans, using Financial Modelling of assumptions validated by the Sales Team.
- Review business cases and ensure investment decisions are made with clear understanding of their impact on net profits.
- Impact merger and acquisition decisions provide Financial due diligence and Financial modeling for a potential acquisition of company in Toronto, Canada.
- Funding and resource allocation drive financial efficiency with divisions with rigorous pressure on costs and a commitment to

value-for-money approach.

- o Re-negotiated contract with service providers, eliminating cost of sales by S\$250k per annum.
- Shared service centre provide reporting and analysis services to Investments team. Tailor reports to business unit requirements.
- Assessing risks to the delivery of projects formulate and drive actions to mitigate them.
- Shareholder value analysis using ROI, ROC. Effective interaction with shareholders whilst appreciating their nonfinancial background.
- Manage project budgets and performance.
- Investigate opportunities as well as high risk and material financial issues, or problem areas, with the business. Develop and propose solutions and options to resolve / progress concerns to a satisfactory outcome
- Develop Employee Stock Option Plan to retain staff.

Day-to-day

- Start-up Finance & Administration Department.
- Management and statutory reporting in IFRS and US GAAP.
- Tax, treasury, risk management.
- Human resources, payroll, company secretarial and administrative functions.
- Handle investors queries with international investors like JP Morgan, Allianz AG, Government of Singapore Investment Corp. etc.
- Efficient corporate tax structure, and contributed to savings in potential tax liability.

Earlier Career:

Apr 1998 to Apr 2000 CHARTERED ASSET MANAGEMENT PTE LTD

Finance & Administration Manager

- Tax structuring for hedge fund based in Mauritius.
- Director of the hedge fund.
- Drive operational improvements.
- Management and statutory reporting for Group (including Malaysia companies) in IFRS
- Tax, treasury, risk management, Human Resource & payroll, company secretarial and administrative functions.

Mar 1996 to Mar 1998 ARTHUR ANDERSEN LLP

Manager, Client Accounting Services

 Manage 15 staff to provide outsourced accounting in US GAAP and IFRS, payroll and GST submission services to clients.

1995 to Feb 1996 L.N. GROUP OF COMPANIES

Finance & Administration Manager

Assist the CFO (former director of Neptune Orient Lines Limited) in :

- Management and statutory reporting.
- Budgeting, forecast and cashflow management

May 1988 to Dec1994 NEPTUNE ORIENT LINES LIMITED

Finance & Administration Manager (IT Subsidiary, Trident Infotech Pte Ltd)

- Start up Finance & Administration Department
- Management and statutory reporting of Singapore and Philippines office.
- Budgeting, forecast and cashflow management
- Tax, treasury, risk management, Human Resource & payroll, company secretarial and administrative functions.

Senior Accountant, Group Budget

 Consolidated the Group Budget and provide quarterly variance analysis.

Jul 1986 to Apr 1988 PRICEWATERHOUSE LLP

Audit Semi-Senior

 Participated in numerous financial audits for organisations of various sizes, such as shipping companies, trading companies, investment banks, manufacturing companies etc.

PROFESSIONAL AFFILIATION

Chartered Accountant ICPAS

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Accountancy National University of Singapore

Post-graduate Diploma in Human Resource Management

Singapore Institute of Management

IT SKILLS

Microsoft Excel, Word, Powerpoint, MYOB, Great Plains, ACCPAC, EasyPay and Fixed Assets.